# **Juan Navas**

### Full Stack Developer



I'm a Full Stack Developer and Computer Science student. I have experience with each layer of web development: frontend, backend, database. Also, I build mobile applications with React Native, Flutter. I'm passionate about technology, never stop learning.

### **Work Experience**

### Intermediate Full Stack Developer

#### Teravision

February 2021 - June 2021 Frontend developer with Next.js.

### Developer

#### Glufco

January 2021 - February 2021 Full stack developer with Vue.js, Laravel and PostgreSQL.

### Full Stack Developer

### Freelance

May 2020 - January 2021

Full stack developer building some projects with React.js, Node.js, Typescript, MongoDB, Flutter, React Native.

### Programmer

#### **FYSS**

August 2018 - April 2020

Full stack developer building some projects with React.js, Node.js, Laravel, MySQL, MongoDB, Docker, Web3.js.

#### Education

## Bachelor of Computer Science Central University of Venezuela 2022

### **Contact Details**

Phone: +58-426-6470654
Email: iam@juannavas.dev
Visit: juannavas.dev
Twitter: @juannavasjn
LinkedIn: juannavasjn
Github: juannavasjn
Gitlab: juannavasjn

#### **Professional Skills**

Team player Software development Problem solving

#### **Software Skills**

Git
Docker
React.js
Node.js
React Native
Flutter
GraphQL
Laravel
AWS, GCP

#### **Personal Skills**

Spanish Language
English Language
Effective communication